Share the music with someone you love.
Music and Lyrics is a comedy, music, romance film directed by Marc Lawrence.
A washed-up '80s pop star gets a chance at a comeback when reigning pop diva Cora Corman invites him to write & record a duet with her, but
there's a problem--Alex hasn't written a song in years; he's never written lyrics and he has to come up with a hit in a matter of days.
Sophie Fisher, played by Drew Barrymore.
Alex Fletcher, played by Hugh Grant.
Chris Riley, played by Brad Garrett.
Cora Corman, played by Haley Bennett.
Janice Stern, played by Brooke Tansley.
Khan, played by Aasif Mandvi.
Music and Lyrics is a 2007 American musical romantic
comedy-drama film written and directed by Marc Lawrence.
It focuses on the relationship that evolves between a former pop music idol (of the fictional band
PoP!) and an aspiring writer as they struggle to compose a song for a reigning pop diva.
The film was released on February 14, 2007, by Warner Bros.
It received mixed-to-positive reviews from critics, who praised Grant's performance and the
musical numbers but found the film simplistic, and grossed $145.9 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of pop star, romcom, has been, songwriting, piano.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.